Sparks Photographs
undated
- Photographs, 1860-1997
  - Ten people around a Model T car including Allie Burwitz and Leland Sparks Sr., undated; UNRS-P2017-13_275; Photographic print; 4 3/8 x 2 3/4 (Box 13)
    Photograph of ten people posing in or around the Ford Model T car. Woman on the left: Allie Burwitz. Man sitting on the car step on the left: Leland Sparks Sr.
  - Leland Sparks Sr. sitting on top of a cliff face, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_276; Photographic print; 2 1/2 x 4 3/8 (Box 13)
    Photograph of a man sitting on the top of a cliff face. Possibly Leland Sparks Sr.
  - Leland Sparks Sr. crossing a stream, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_277; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 13)
    Photograph of a man wading through a stream. The man is wearing a white shirt and black pants. Possibly Leland Sparks Sr.
  - Leland Sparks Sr. standing in a stream with a long pole, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_278; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 13)
    Photograph of a man standing in a stream with a long pole. Possibly Leland Sparks Sr.
  - Leland Sparks Sr. standing at the edge of a stream, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_279; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 13)
    Photograph of a man standing at the edge of a stream looking back toward the photographer. Possibly Leland Sparks Sr.
  - Four men changing a tire on a car, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_280; Photographic print; 2 5/8 x 4 3/8 (Box 13)
    Photograph of four men standing in the road. The second man from the right is holding a car tire in front of a bike pump. No identification.
  - Leland Sparks Sr. with camp cooking equipment, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_281; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 13)
    Photograph of a man standing by camp cooking equipment. Possibly Leland Sparks Sr.
  - Two men replacing a tire on a car, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_282; Photographic print; 4 1/4 x 2 5/8 (Box 13)
    Photograph of two men working on replacing a tire on the Model T car while a woman walks further along the road. No identification.
  - Three women and two men sitting in a Model T., October 5, 1913; UNRS-P2017-13_283; Photographic print; 4 1/4 x 2 3/8 (Box 13)
    Photograph of three men and two women sitting in a Model T. Caption on image: Oct 5, 1913 Williams, Calif. No identification.
  - Four women standing next to a Model T., undated; UNRS-P2017-13_284; Photographic print; 4 3/8 x 2 1/2 (Box 13)
    Photograph of four women standing around a Model T on a city street. No identification.
  - Three women and two men sitting in a Model T., undated; UNRS-P2017-13_285; Photographic print; 4 1/4 x 2 1/2 (Box 13)
    Photograph of two men and three women sitting in a Model T car. Caption on image: While visiting in Gidly. No identification.
  - Mr. Walther and Leland Sparks Sr., undated; UNRS-P2017-13_286; Photographic print; 2 1/2 x 4 1/4 (Box 13)
    Photograph of two men standing in front of a building. Caption on image: Mr. Walther and Papa. "Papa" is Leland Sparks Sr.
  - Mr. Walther and Leland Sparks Sr. in front of a fountain, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_287; Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 13)
    Photograph of Mr. Walther and Leland Sparks Sr. standing in front of a stone fountain and water wheel. Caption on image: Mr. Walther and Papa.
  - Woman in a fur coat and hat, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_288; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 1 3/4 (Box 13)
    Photograph of a woman in a fur coat and hat with buildings in the background. No identification.
  - Man in a suit in front of a service depot, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_289; Photographic print; 2 5/8 x 2 5/8 (Box 13)
    Photograph of a man in a suit and hat standing on a street. Behind him is a building with a sign saying "service dept." No identification.
  - Store front of Firestone Tire & Rubber Company, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_290; Photographic print; 4 1/4 x 2 5/8 (Box 13)
    Photograph of the Firestone Tire and Rubber Company store front. Firestone is a company where Leland Sparks Sr. was an executive while living in San Francisco around WWII.
  - Allie Burwitz in a long coat and fur scarf in a park, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_291; Photographic print; 2 5/8 x 4 3/8 (Box 13)
    Photograph of Allie Burwitz in a long coat standing on a grassy block in a city.
  - Leland Sparks Sr. and a man in front of a car, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_292; Photographic print; 4 1/4 x 2 5/8 (Box 13)
    Photograph of two men standing in front of a car. Leland Sparks Sr. is on the left.
  - Allie and a salesman with Firestone in front of the store, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_293; Photographic print; 2 1/2 x 4 1/4 (Box 13)
    Photographic of a man and Allie Burwitz standing in front of the Firestone store. Caption on the image: one of the salesmen of Firestone.
  - Two men and two women on a park trail, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_294; Photographic print; 4 3/8 x 2 3/4 (Box 13)
    Photograph of two men and two women standing on a park trail near a fountain. No identification.
  - Woman standing next to two cows, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_295; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/8 (Box 13)
    Photograph of woman standing next to two cows in the field. No identification.
  - Two women and a man lying in a field, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_296; Photographic print; 4 3/8 x 2 5/8 (Box 13)
    Photograph of two women and one man laying in a field. No identification.
  - Four men and a woman standing in a field, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_297; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 5/8 (Box 13)
    Photograph of four men and one woman standing in a field. No identification.
  - Man walking toward Mother B’s geese, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_298; Photographic print; 2 5/8 x 4 1/8 (Box 13)
    Photograph of a man walking toward five geese in a yard. Behind him is a garden and some farm buildings. No identification. Caption on image: Mother B's Geese, Cornelius.
  - Four women and a man sitting in a field, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_299; Photographic print; 4 3/8 x 2 5/8 (Box 13)
    Photograph of one man and four women sitting in a field. No identification.
  - Ruth Searles Sparks in a dress suit and feathered hat, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_300; Photographic print; 2 1/4 x 3 1/4 (Box 13)
    Photograph of a women in a dress suit wearing a feathered hat. Caption on image: Ruth Searles Sparks.
  - Ruth Searles Sparks in a plaid dress, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_301; Photographic print; 2 1/8 x 3 (Box 13)
    Photograph of a woman in a checkered dress holding an umbrella. Possibly Ruth Searles Sparks.
  - Ruth Searles Sparks sitting on a park bench, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_302; Photographic print; 2 x 3 1/8 (Box 13)
    Photograph of Ruth Searles Sparks in a dress suit wearing a feathered hat. She is sitting on a park bench.
  - Ruth Searles Sparks sitting on stairs leading to a front porch, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_303; Photographic print; 2 1/4 x 3 1/8 (Box 13)
    Photograph of Ruth Searles Sparks wearing a white shirt and dark skirt. She is sitting on a staircase. Caption on image: Ruth Seales Sparks.
  - Ruth Searles Sparks standing in front of a tent, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_304; Photographic print; 2 1/4 x 2 1/8 (Box 13)
    Photograph of a woman in a checkered dress holding an umbrella over her shoulder. Behind her is a tent with the flaps open. Possibly Ruth Searles Sparks.
  - Man wearing a tank top and shorts, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_305; Photographic print; 3/4 x 2 3/8 (Box 13)
    Photograph of a man standing on a deck in a tanktop and shorts. No identification.
  - Ruth Searles Sparks lying on grass, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_306; Photographic print; 2 1/4 x 2 (Box 13)
    Photograph of Ruth Searles Sparks wearing a white shirt and dark skirt. She is laying on some grass with her right arm behind her head.
  - Ruth Searles Sparks sitting on grass, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_307; Photographic print; 3 1/4 x 2 1/4 (Box 13)
    Photograph of Ruth Searles Sparks wearing a white shirt and dark skirt. She is sitting on the grass with a house in the background.
  - Ruth Searles Sparks sitting on grass wearing a hat, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_308; Photographic print; 3 1/8 x 2 1/4 (Box 13)
    Photograph of Ruth Searles Sparks wearing a white shirt, dark skirt, and feathered hat. She is sitting on the grass with a house in the background.
  - Ruth Searles Sparks holding a stick, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_309; Photographic print; 1 1/4 x 2 (Box 13)
    Photograph of a woman checkered dress sitting next to a tree holding a stick. She is possibly Ruth Searles Sparks.
  - Allie Burwitz wearing a sailor’s dress, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_310; Photographic print; 2 1/2 x 3 1/4 (Box 13)
    Photograph of Allie Burwitz in a dark dress with a sailor's neckerchief and hat. She is examining something in her hands.
  - Woman sitting on a beach with a satchel, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_311; Photographic print; 1 7/8 x 2 1/8 (Box 13)
    Photograph of a woman in a dark dress with dark gloves. She is sitting on a sandy beach and has a satchel. No identification.
  - Allie Burwitz wearing a sailor’s dress, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_312; Photographic print; 2 1/8 x 3 1/4 (Box 13)
    Photograph of Allie Burwitz in a dark dress with a sailor's neckerchief and hat. She is smiling at the camera.
  - Four women in sailor’s dresses, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_313; Photographic print; 3 3/8 x 3 1/4 (Box 13)
    Photograph of four women in sailors dresses posing on a beach scene. No identification.
  - Woman in a swimming dress, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_314; Photographic print; 3 3/8 x 3 5/8 (Box 13)
    Faded photograph of a woman in a swimming dress at the beach. No identification.
  - Two women laying in the beach surf, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_315; Photographic print; 3 3/8 x 3 3/4 (Box 13)
    Faded photograph of two women laying in the water at the beach. No identification.
  - Two women in swim suits and caps lying on a beach, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_316; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 13)
    Photograph of two women in swim suits and caps laying on the beach. No identification.
  - Two women and a man sitting at the beach, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_317; Photographic print; 2 3/8 x 2 1/4 (Box 13)
    Photograph of two men and a woman sitting at the beach. No identification.
  - Two women in swim suits and caps lying on a beach, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_318; Photographic print; 3 x 2 1/2 (Box 13)
  - Six people sitting on rocks by a bridge, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_319; Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 2 1/2 (Box 13)
    Photograph of six people sitting and standing on rocks by a bridge. No identification.
  - Group of men standing in front of a car, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_320; Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 2 1/2 (Box 13)
    Photograph of mostly men standing in front of a car. No identification.
  - Women and children standing in front of a car, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_321; Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 2 1/2 (Box 13)
    Photograph of women and children standing in front of a car. No identification.
  - Women and children in swim suits, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_322; Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 2 1/2 (Box 13)
    Photograph of women and children in swim suits standing and sitting in front of some trees. No identification.
  - Women and children in front of a house, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_323; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 3 7/8 (Box 13)
    Faded photo of women and children in front of a house. No identification.
  - Young girl standing behind a stone wall, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_324; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 3 5/8 (Box 13)
    Photograph of a young girl standing behind a stone wall with a flower in her hair. No identification.
  - Fourteen boys and girls at a birthday party, 1924; UNRS-P2017-13_325; Photographic print; 6 x 4 (Box 13)
    Photograph of fourteen boys and girls sitting on a staircase. They are surrounded by balloons. Caption on image: 4 yr. old. No identification.
  - Fourteen boys and girls at a birthday party, 1924; UNRS-P2017-13_326; Photographic print; 2 5/8 x 4 1/2 (Box 13)
    Photograph of fourteen boys and girls sitting on a staircase. They are surrounded by balloons. Taken from the same occasion at photo 00325. No identification.
  - Ten girls sitting on a staircase at a birthday party, June 16, 1925; UNRS-P2017-13_327; Photographic print; 4 3/8 x 2 3/4 (Box 13)
    Photograph of ten girls sitting on a staircase. Most likely from the same 5 year old birthday party for Nancy Lee Sparks in photo 00328. No identification.
  - Ten girls sitting on a staircase at a birthday party, June 16, 1926; UNRS-P2017-13_328; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 13)
    Photograph of ten girls sitting on a staircase. Caption on image: 5th birthday party. June 16, 1925. Most likely from a birthday party for Nancy Lee Sparks. No identification.
  - Three girls standing under a tree, March 1925; UNRS-P2017-13_329; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 13)
    Photograph of three girls standing in front of a tree in bloom. Caption on image: Blossom fete. Saratoga, Cal. Mch 1925. Majorie Jean & Helen Neston. No identification within photo.
  - Three girls sitting under a tree, March 1925; UNRS-P2017-13_330; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 13)
    Photograph of three girls sitting underneath a tree in full bloom. The same girls in photo 00329. Taken in Saratoga, California during March of 1925. No identification.
  - Leland Sparks Sr. with four men and a woman outside a building, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_331; Photographic print; 4 x 2 1/2 (Box 13)
    Photograph of five men and one woman sitting or standing outside of a house. The man standing on the left is Leland Sparks Sr.
  - Leland Sparks Sr. with three men outside a building, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_332; Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 13)
    Photograph of four men standing by a house. The second man from the left is Leland Sparks Sr.
  - S. S. “Leviathan”, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_333; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 1/2 (Box 13)
    Postcard of the S.S. Leviathian. Caption on front: S. S. "Leviathan." The world's largest liner driven by oil fuel. Length 950 ft. Breadth 100 ft. Accomodation 4,500. Gross Tonnage 59,956. 66,000 HP. 4 1/2 times round Promenade Deck 1 mile. Published by the Ocean Trading Co., Southampton.
  - Social Hall on the S. S. “Leviathan”, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_334; Postcard; 3 1/2 x 5 3/8 (Box 13)
    Postcard of men and women sitting in chairs in a lounge. Caption on image: "Cosy corner of the social hall. 1st class, S. S. 'Leviathan.'" Published by the Ocean Trading Co., Southampton.
  - Dining Saloon in the S. S. “Leviathan”, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_335; Postcard; 5 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 13)
    Postcard of an elaborate dining hall with tables covered in white tablecloths. Caption on image: "Dining Saloon, 1st. Class, S. S. Leviathan" Published by the Ocean Trading Co., Southampton.
  - Winter garden and foyer on the S. S. “Leviathan”, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_336; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 1/2 (Box 13)
    Postcard of a dining area up a staircase with palm trees on either side of the staircase. Caption on image: "Winter Garden & Palm Foyer. 1st. Class, S. S. Leviathan" Published by the Ocean Trading Co., Southampton.
  - Library and writing room on the S. S. “Leviathan”, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_337; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 1/2 (Box 13)
    Postcard of leather chairs in a room with tables and lamps near each group of chairs. Caption on image: "Library and writing room, S. S. Leviathan" Published by the Ocean Trading Co., Southampton.
  - Tea room on the S. S. “Leviathan”, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_338; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 3/8 (Box 13)
    Photograph of floral patterned chairs surrounding wooden tables. Caption on the image: "Tea room, 1st. Class, S. S. Leviathan" Published by the Ocean Trading Co., Southampton.
  - Swimming pool on the S. S. “Leviathan”, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_339; Postcard; 5 3/8 x 3 1/2 (Box 13)
    Postcard of three women in swimsuits near the ladder for a large pool. The pool is surrounded by large columns and has a double staircase leading up from the pooldeck. Caption on the image: "Swimming pool, 1st. Class, S. S. Leviathan."
  - Leland John Sparks Sr., undated; UNRS-P2017-13_340; Photographic Print; 7 3/8 x 9 1/2 Copy 1 was ripped in half and carefully realigned and taped along the edges of the photograph. (Box 13)
    Photograph of Leland Sparks Sr. He is wearing a suit and tie.
    There are two copies of this photograph. Copy 1: Photograph was ripped in half, but both pieces were still with the album. Photographer was Charles M. Hiller. From an album belonging to Allie Burwitz, Leland Sparks Sr.'s wife. The album has a mottled cover with black leaf pages. Located in Box 3, Folder 3. Copy 2: Caption around image: Allie's Husband and Father of Nancy Lee & Leland Jr./Leland John Sparks. Photograph is located in a photo album commemorating the centennial birthday of the year. Located in Box 12
    Copy 1 was removed from the album for repair and sleeving
  - Nancy Lee Sparks, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_341; Photographic Print; 1 3/8 x 1 1/2 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Photograph of Nancy Lee Sparks wearing a thin striped blouse with a small broach.
    From the album belonging to Nancy Sparks, the daughter of Leland Sparks Sr. The album has a light brown cover with four gold lines on the left side of the album cover
    Removed from the album belonging to Nancy Sparks, the daughter of Leland Sparks Sr. The album has a light brown cover with four gold lines on the left side of the album cover.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks in uniform, 1945; UNRS-P2017-13_342; Copy 1: Photographic print; 3 1/2 x 4 1/2 Copy 2: Photographic print; 3 x 3 7/8 Copy 3: Photographic print; 5 x 7 (Box 11)
    Photograph of Nancy Lee Sparks in her Navy uniform.
    There are three copies of this photo. Copy 1: Located in an album belonging to Nancy Sparks, the daughter of Leland Sparks Sr. The album has a light brown cover with four gold lines on the left side of the album cover. The leaves of the album have been unscrewed from the cover and left in original order. Located in Box 12 Copy 2: Located in Box 3, Folder 5 Copy 3: Located in Box 3, Folder 5
  - Nancy Lee Sparks, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_343; Photographic print; 6 7/8 x 4 7/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of Nancy Lee Sparks sitting behind a desk with papers under her arms.
    Located in an album belonging to Nancy Sparks, the daughter of Leland Sparks Sr. The album has a light brown cover with four gold lines on the left side of the album cover. The leaves of the album have been unscrewed from the cover and left in original order.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_344; Photographic print; 2 1/4 x 2 3/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of Nancy Lee Sparks standing outside. She is wearing a pink dress.
  - Unidentified woman with her legs buried at a beach, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_345; Photographic print; 2 1/2 x 1 7/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a woman in a floral shirt and bandana sitting on a beach with her legs covered in sand. No identification. Same woman as in photo 00346.
  - Unidentified woman with her legs buried at a beach, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_346; Photographic print; 2 1/2 x 1 7/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a woman in a floral shirt and bandana sitting on a beach with her legs covered in sand. No identification. Same woman as in photo 00345.
  - Two boys and a woman sitting on a beach, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_347; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 1 7/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of two boys and a woman sitting on a beach. No identification.
  - Four people sitting behind a house, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_348; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 1 7/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of four people behind a house. There are two women sitting on a bench, a boy standing at the corner of the bench, and another man kneeling next to a dog in front of the bench. No identification.
  - Four people laying in a pile of hay, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_349; Photographic print; 2 1/8 x 2 7/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of three girls and one boy laying on a haystack in a field. No identification.
  - Three people laying on a bed, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_350; Photographic print; 2 7/8 x 1 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of three people laying on a bed/couch. There is a table in the foreground. No identification.
  - Eight people sitting on a pile of hay, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_351; Photographic print; 3 x 1 7/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of six women and one boy sitting on a haystack in a field. No identification.
  - Three people laying on a bed, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_352; Photographic print; 3 1/8 x 1 7/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of three people laying on a bed under blankets. No identification.
  - Boy standing on a front lawn, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_353; Photographic print; 2 7/8 x 2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a boy standing on the front lawn of a two story house. He is in a white shirt and white pants. No identification.
  - Woman in a dress suit sitting on a lawn, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_354; Photographic print; 3 x 2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a woman in a dress suit sitting on the grass of a front lawn. No identification.
  - Boy sitting on a lawn, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_355; Photographic print; 2 7/8 x 2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a boy sitting on the grass of a front lawn. No identification.
  - Woman in a dress suit in front of a bush, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_356; Photographic print; 1 1/2 x 3 1/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a woman standing in front of a bush. She is wearing a white dress suit and holding some flowers. No identification.
  - Maud MacKenzie’s mansion in Carmel, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_357; Photographic print; 3 3/4 x 1 7/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of Maud Sparks MacKenzie's mansion in Carmel, California. There is a shoreline which curves around the bay in the background.
  - Arial view of a city with a sports stadium, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_358; Photographic print; 3 5/8 x 1 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of an aerial view of a city with a sports stadium in the foreground and a steeple in the right middle ground.
  - Group of nine women dressed for travel, undated; UNRS-P2017-13_359; Photographic print; 4 1/8 x 2 1/8 (Box 11)
    Photograph of nine women in large overcoats. Some are holding blankets. No identification.
  - Counselor’s day off at the Contra Costa Vacation Camp, 1941; UNRS-P2017-13_360; Photographic print; 6 x 4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of two men and two women sitting on a beach with a picnic and smoking pipes or cigarettes. Caption around image: Contra Costa Vacation Camp - Summer 1941, Mendocino Woodlands. Counselors' Day-Off - Beach above Fort Bragg. Dottie Lancaster, Leo Ball, N.L.S., Ted Aarons. Third from the right is Nancy Lee Sparks.
  - Dottie Lancaster sitting in a field of grass, 1941; UNRS-P2017-13_361; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a woman sitting on some grass watching a boy playing. Most likely at the Contra Costa Vacation Camp in the Mendocino Woodlands. Caption under image: Dottie Lancaster.
  - Ted Harons, 1941; UNRS-P2017-13_362; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of a man holding something indistinct in his hands. Caption under image: Ted Aarons. Most likely at the Contra Costa Vacation Camp in the Mendocino Woodlands.
  - Dottie Lancaster, 1941; UNRS-P2017-13_363; Photographic print; 2 3/4 x 4 1/2 (Box 11)
    Photograph of Dottie Lancaster sitting in a field. Caption under image: D.L. Most likely at the Contra Costa Vacation Camp in the Mendocino Woodlands.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks with four children, 1941; UNRS-P2017-13_364; Photographic print; 4 1/2 x 2 3/4 (Box 11)
    Photograph of four children and Nancy Lee Sparks standing in front of a hedge. Tentative identification: Back row: unidentified; middle row: Willie Ives, Bruce Johnson, Billy Abbot; front row: Stuart Kingman. Most likely at the Contra Costa Vacation Camp in the Mendocino Woodlands.
  - Nancy Lee Sparks, 1941; UNRS-P2017-13_365; Photographic print; 2 1/2 x 3 1/2 (Box 11)